https://www.orconind.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Orcon Industries
Skip to main content
Call 585-768-7000
Facebook Twitter LinkedIn
8715 Lake RoadLeRoy, NY 14482 Get a Quote for Custom Packaging
Wood
Custom PalletsOn-Site CratingWooden Shipping Crates and Containers
Void Fill
AirPlusFoamPlusPaperPlus Shooters
About
Capabilities
ContactCall (585) 768-70008715 Lake RoadLeRoy, NY 14482Get a Quote for Custom Packaging
Privacy Policy
April 1, 2018
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for orconind.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (585) 768-7000 or info@orconind.com.
Stay Up To Date
Be the first to learn about the latest tools and technology to solve your most challenging packaging needs.
Mailing List Signup
If you are human, leave this field blank.
There Was a Call for Help. We Were Happy To Answer.
In 2020, our mission is to continue to provide industry-leading packaging solutions to companies that rely on us to protect their valuable assets.
Now more than ever, companies need scalable strategies that prioritize sustainability, and we’re poised to take on the challenges.
